WONG, Wai Ha, Cathy

Flat 8H, Yick Fai Building, Sai Ching Street, Yuen Long, NT • 9866-4473 • cathy115hk@yahoo.com.hk

PROFILE

I love Accounting and I have learnt Accounting for almost 8 years. I have a passion for working as a professional accountant to put what I have learnt into my work. I am taking the professional examination to be a Certified Public Accountant, and target to be Qualified within 4 years.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Immediate available
- Multi-tasking
- Independent
- Able to work under pressure and meet deadlines
- Accurate

- Bachelor degree in Accountancy
- 4 years accounting and auditing experience
- Effective problem solving skills
- Efficient time management
- Familiar with Accounting operations
- Strong sense of responsibility

WORK EXPERIENCES

Nov 2012 - Feb 2017 Chu & Lo Co., CPA

Intermediate Audit Officer

Chu & Lo Co. is a Certified Public Accountant which provides auditing, accounting, company secretary and consulting services for local and overseas companies.

- Conducted audit assignments independently by examining the accounts of companies to ensure the validity and legality of their financial records
- Handled full set of accounts
- Prepared tax computation and schedules for tax compliance
- Liaised with managerial staff and presented findings and recommendations
- Prepared audited reports and statements in tight deadline
- Provided guidance to junior staff and preformed overall review of deliverables

May 2012 - Sep 2012 Procon CPA Limited, CPA

Audit Officer

Procon CPA Limited is a Certified Public Accountant which provides mainly auditing services to SMEs in both Hong Kong and Mainland China

- Assisted in auditing companies including setting up the engagement, preparing the audit works and audited financial statements, and collecting audit evidence in clients' offices
- Handled monthly accounting transactions for non-profit organization

Jun 2010 -Mar 2011

Goodwill Accountancy Services Company Part-time Accounting Assistant
Goodwill Accountancy Services Company provides auditing, accounting, company
secretary and consulting services to SMEs

- Handled full set of manufacturing companies accounting transactions
- Assisted in auditing companies including revising final financial statement for Inland Revenue Department and collecting audit evidence in clients' offices in Mainland China and Hong Kong
- Worked with clients in preparing Annual Returns

EDUCATION

Sep 2008 - Feb 2012 City University of Hong Kong (CityU)

Bachelor of Business Administration in Accountancy Minor in Business Economics

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Apr 2009 - May 2010 City Youth Empowerment Project

Volunteer

- Helped students with dyslexia to study
- Visited elderly home to help them clean houses

Dec 2009 - Jan 2010 Guangzhou Sun Yat-sen University (SYSU) Exchange Program Participant

- Resided in and attended lectures at SYSU covering China accounting, China Taxation and corporate governance practices in China
- Exchanged ideas with SYSU students on relevant international and Chinese accounting and taxation issues
- Visited Chinese companies and met the management personnel to get firsthand information

Jan 2009 - Jan 2010 CityU Students' Union Publication Department

Sub-committeeman

- Published and designed School Calendar
- Reported on the current affairs of Students' Union and published other articles to promote students' sense of belonging
- Performed other administrative duties

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

2011 Hong Kong St. John Ambulance – First Aid Certificate

2009 CityU Student Development Services - Certificate of Completion in Peer

Helping & Counseling Skills

2008 LCCI- Level 3 (Distinction)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Qualification Student member of Hong Kong Certified Public Accountants

IT Skills Proficient PC knowledge in MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint and MYOB

Typing English: 45 wpm, Chinese: 40 wpm

Languages Fluent English, Mandarin and Cantonese

Availability Immediate available

Current salary \$16,500

Expected Salary \$17,500 - \$20,000 (negotiable)